<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<content>
	<chooseBalance>
		<popupWindow>
			<text>Welcome to the Acquire - Choose Balance Module. In this module, we will help you learn about the weight limitations of the balances. By the end of this lesson, you will understand when is the right time to use a Microbalance and a Semi-Microbalance.</text>
		</popupWindow>
		<section>
			<listText>Microbalance</listText>
			<step>
				<listText>Intro</listText>
				<descriptionText>This a Microbalance, it is the more sensitive of the two balances we will be using. Because it is extremely sensitive, it is used to weight materials with its precision in the fractions of a milligram. It is made up of two hardware components: one for user input and the other to weigh materials.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Specifications</listText>
				<descriptionText>As said before, Microbalances are a lot more precise than Semi-Microbalances. They are more sensitive but they can support less weight than their counterpart. This microbalance has a Weight Capacity 5g (grams) and a Precision of 1µg (microgram) = 0.000001 grams.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Models</listText>
				<descriptionText>The balance displayed is the Sartorius ME5. Depending on the balance being used, it will have a different Weight Capacity, and Precision.

Note: Always refer to your balance’s User Manual to find its specifications.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Body</listText>
				<descriptionText>Microbalances are usually made up of two body parts. One of them is the terminal you use when inputting information, the other holds the pan and all the sensitive mechanisms to weigh objects. These are connected via a cable.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Draft Shield</listText>
				<descriptionText>Microbalances also feature draft shields. They encapsulate the weighing chamber where the weighing pan and weighing materials are located. Draft shields prevent wind drafts from altering measurements. The draft shield on this balance is one that rotates and is controlled by buttons on the terminal.</descriptionText>
			</step>
		</section>
		<section>
			<listText>Semi-Microbalance</listText>
			<step>
				<listText>Intro</listText>
				<descriptionText>This a Semi-Microbalance, it is used to weigh objects of more mass than the ones weighed on a Microbalance.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Specifications</listText>
				<descriptionText>Semi-Microbalances can weigh objects that are a lot more massive that the Microbalance. They trade off some precision for higher weight yield. This semi-microbalance has a Weight Capacity 210g (grams) and a Precision of 0.0001g (grams).</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Models</listText>
				<descriptionText>The balance displayed is the Sartorius AZ214. Depending on the balance being used, it will have a different Weight Capacity, and Precision.

Note: Always refer to your balance’s User Manual to find its specifications.</descriptionText>
			</step>
				<step>
					<listText>Body</listText>
					<descriptionText>Semi-Microbalances consists of only one body part that houses both the weighing mechanisms and the user terminal.</descriptionText>
				</step>
				<step>
					<listText>Draft Shield</listText>
					<descriptionText>Semi-Microbalances also feature draft shields. They encapsulate the weighing chamber where the weighing pan and weighing materials are located. Draft shields prevent wind drafts from altering measurements. The draft shield on this balance consist of sliding doors that are manipulated by using the handles.</descriptionText>
				</step>
		</section>
		<section>
			<listText>Choosing a Balance</listText>
			<step>
				<listText>Weights</listText>
				<descriptionText>This is a calibration weight. There are many shapes and sizes but we will be using these for our examples and calibration. These weights have their mass engraved on the face of their top side</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Determining What Balance to Choose</listText>
				<descriptionText>Trying to weigh something that is larger than the balance’s maximum weight can damage its components so you must use a balance with a higher weight yield. If you are given a material and told to weigh a certain amount of it, you would choose the balance that can support the weight and give you the most accurate measurement.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Scenario</listText>
				<descriptionText>This is a 20g weight. Which would be the correct balance to weigh this material? Press “Next” to find out.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Correct Balance</listText>
				<descriptionText>The correct balance would be the Semi-Microbalance. A microbalance cannot support anything over 5g in weight so using that one is out of the question. The Semi-Microbalance can support up to 210g so it is the only viable option.</descriptionText>
			</step>
		</section>
	</chooseBalance>
	<prepareBalance>
		<popupWindow>
			<!-- Add text to popup -->
			<text></text>
		</popupWindow>
		<step>
			<listText>Calibration Label</listText>
			<descriptionText></descriptionText>
		</step>
		<section>
			<listText>Level Balance</listText>
			<step>
				<listText>Bubble Level</listText>
				<descriptionText>The bubble level lets you know if your balance is on a level surface. The balance is leveled when the air bubble is within the circle drawn on the center of the glass.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Leveling Screws</listText>
				<descriptionText>In the case that the balance is not level, twist these screws to raise or lower the balance corners. Shifting the height of the balance’s individual corners levels the balance.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Adjusting the Screws</listText>
				<descriptionText>From back here it is possible to adjust the leveling screws while having a clear view of the bubble level.</descriptionText>
			</step>
		</section>
		<section>
			<listText>Clean Balance</listText>
			<step>
				<listText>Problem Areas</listText>
				<descriptionText>Dirty and grime accumulates on the weigh pan and the few mechanisms under it.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Importance of Cleaning</listText>
				<descriptionText>If left uncleaned for a prolonged amount of time, the balance’s reading will begin to suffer.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Tools to Use When Cleaning</listText>
				<descriptionText>A brush and water or alcohol is used to clean these components.</descriptionText>
			</step>
		</section>
	</prepareBalance>
	<calibrateBalance>
		<popupWindow>
			<text>Welcome to the Acquire - Balance Calibration Module. In this module, we will help you learn about the calibration procedure the balances. By the end of this lesson, you will understand how to perform calibration of a balance.</text>
		</popupWindow>
		<step>
			<listText>Turn Balance On</listText>
			<descriptionText>First, turn on the balance using the on/off button.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<section>
			<listText>Perform Weight Check</listText>
			<step>
				<listText>Intro</listText>
				<descriptionText>It is important to perform a weight check every time you use a balance to ensure that the readings you are recording are correct.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Activate Calibration Mode</listText>
				<descriptionText>To enter Calibration Mode, hold the tare button down till you hear a beep.

Note: Different balances enter Calibration Mode in different ways. Refer to your specific balance’s user manual.
Show user 200g calibration weight
</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>The Calibration Weight</listText>
				<descriptionText>This is a calibration weight. It is used when calibrating a balance to ensure that the balance is in a working condition.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Open Door</listText>
				<descriptionText>If the door isn't already open, open it to gain access to the weighing chamber.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Place the Weight</listText>
				<descriptionText>Place the calibration weight on the weighing pan.</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Close Door</listText>
				<descriptionText>Close the door. This keeps wind drafts from affecting the balance reading. The door are also referred to as "Draft Shields".</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Wait for Reading to Stabilize</listText>
				<descriptionText>Wait 10 seconds until the balance beeps. Congratulations your balance is now calibrated!</descriptionText>
			</step>
			<step>
				<listText>Remove Calibration Weight</listText>
				<descriptionText>Remove the calibration weight from the weigh pan.</descriptionText>
			</step>
		</section>
		<step>
			<listText>Add Weight Container</listText>
			<descriptionText>Some materials will require a weight container to hold them while using the balance. Place the weight container on the weigh pan.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Make Sure Door is Closed</listText>
			<descriptionText>Make sure the door is closed to ensure a proper reading!</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Tare</listText>
			<descriptionText>Tare out the weight container before adding the weighing material.</descriptionText>
		</step>
	</calibrateBalance>
	<useBalance>
		<popupWindow>
			<!-- Need text for this popup. -->
			<text></text>
		</popupWindow>
		<step>
			<listText>Open Door</listText>
			<descriptionText>Open the draft shield door.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Add Desired Material</listText>
			<descriptionText>Add desired material to the weight container.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Make Sure Door is Closed</listText>
			<descriptionText>Make sure the draft shield door is closed.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Wait for Reading to Stabilize</listText>
			<descriptionText>The readout display will not give the correct weight after the material is added. You must wait until the numbers stop fluctuating to consider the reading valid.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Record Weight</listText>
			<descriptionText>Record the weight on the readout display.</descriptionText>
		</step>
		<step>
			<listText>Note: On Hygiene</listText>
			<descriptionText>It is standard procedure and a common courtesy to clean the balance after use if any spills occurred during operation.</descriptionText>
		</step>
	</useBalance>
</content>